<resources>
    <string name="app_name">cruddygame</string>
    <string name="story0">The construct of ones person can feel stalwart from the years spent on it. But truth be told even the strongest masters are close to death when asleep. And sages can change immensely through one idea. As you pitter-patter through your existence, and think of all the things you have gained, realize that the day will come that you wake up an entirely different person. No one can stop a flowing river, and the sands of time fall ever down. And though the light is strong and it shines rays and blinks and lights the way, the darkness is the only constant. Lights fade eventually. Flee your fate desperately. And though you change from day to day, one day at the end of time you will be one with the dark void.</string>
    <string name="story1">That was the strangest dream I can ever remember having. A soft and low voice spoke the words to me with no images popping into my mind’s eye. I thought about the words spoken to me. Everything must end one day, right? But that wasn’t what caught my mind, I was stuck on the question - could you wake up a different person? Have your entire being changed in one day? I strolled into the marketplace. \n
        There was a consistent murmur throughout. I walked up to two people talking loudly. \n
        “Everyone in town had a creepy dream last night! There must be witches about!” \n
        “You don’t know what you are yelling ‘bout! I slept like a baby! This town is just soft and scared of a storm!” \n
        “You slept like a baby because you can barely understand English! You probably didn’t understand the words and forgot about it! There is evil afoot! We should get an army together!” \n
        “All we need is the fists right here you moron!” \n
        He lifted his hands up and lunged towards the other man. I continued circling the marketplace. \n
        “It told me that I would fall asleep peacefully” \n
        “It told me that I will never achieve my dreams” \n
        “The voice told me to sacrifice myself to the void” \n
        Everyone heard different things from the voice in their dreams, but all of them were told that they would be one with the dark void.
    </string>
    <string name="story2">I saw a crowd gathered by one of the fortune tellers in the marketplace. One renowned for giving correct predictions. This old and craggily woman commanded everyone’s attention as she spoke. \n
        “The void walkers have returned. They bring the horrors of the void. With your dreams they seek to create darkness and doubt within your heart and use you to create a void. Beware, they are strong from spending time in the void. I am afraid that the void they make will consume everything. There is no fighting it. We will all become one with the void.” \n
        This disturbed much of the crowd who knew her powers for themselves, but a large group was in disbelief and began to yell at her and accuse her of being responsible for everyone’s dreams. The old woman began to run away from the enraged crowd demanding answers. I also wanted answers, so I ran after her. Me and the crowd ran after this surprisingly spry old woman. She twisted around the inner workings of the town. Many people tried to circle around through other alleyways to cut her off. Soon I was completely alone and lost in the middle of twisted alleys. I walked along the streets, trying to just make my way back to my home. The sun was setting and I was getting tired of circling the streets, lost. I turned a corner to a dead end and decided to sit down and wait to walk around in the cool of night. I was sitting and suddenly noticed a figure the color of the wall jutting out. It was the old woman disguised as the wall. I jumped, startled by the small and bent figure. I looked at her silently.
    </string>
    <string name="story3">
        “You were with the crowd chasing me, but you mean me no harm, correct?” \n
        I nodded \n
        “So you seek answers?” \n
        I nodded \n
        “Is there no way to avoid the void?” I asked \n
        She breathed deeply and sighed. \n
        “I’m afraid not, I have seen what I have seen. But take heart, there is life in the void, twisted as it may be. Many will die, but the strong will survive.” \n
        “But what if we resist the void? Can we overpower life there and establish our civilization again?” \n
        She smiled at me with pity. \n
        “I have not been able to see that much, but I believe it to be an impossible task, Life there is too strong. We have no warriors here that can deal with the strongest being’s strength. Not even Barab, the captain of the guard can defeat them. But if I cannot see that far in the future, then there is some decision I cannot see past. There is an event that is not set and could go either way. I am just afraid that either way would end poorly for us. As slaves or corpses.” \n
        “how long do we have before the void comes?” \n
        “I do not know, child, but there are ways to prolong its coming."

    </string>

    <string name="story4">
        At that moment I maade a decision. I would wake up tomorrow a different person. I would wake up a warrior. Or mage, whichever one. \n
        “Old hag, I have decided to fight the void. Tell me what I have to do.” \n
        She smiled another pity smile and said \n
        “You are laughably weak child, and laughably foolish. Yet you are the only person who believed me and was not seized in terror. Here take this and come meet me in my home tomorrow.” \n
        She handed me a thin piece of bamboo that was carved into the shape of a diagger. \n
        At the end of our conversation someone found us in the ally. A large man sporting a large sword. \n
        “Prepare to die witch!” \n
        As soon as he had drawn his sword he burst into flames. He screeched and yelled until he turned entirely into ash. The old hag could have killed me and the whole crowd at any second she wanted to back in the marketplace. She was powerful to be sure, but now I also knew that she was benevolent for sure, and that we would take on the void together. I looked at her and asked her one final question. \n
        “How do I get out of these alleys?” \n
        She smiled one last smile. This one was more mischievous than the other ones. My limbs stiffened up and I collapsed. I soon fell unconscious. \n
    </string>
    <string name="story5">
        I woke up in my bed and stood up, feeling refreshed. I thought about my day and my goal now. My life was going to be completely changed. Time to go visit the old hag.
    </string>

    <string name="story7">
        I walked over to the Witch’s house, which turned out to be a small thatch hut.  The only opening was an animal pelt. Not wanting to come in unannounced I called into the hut. \n
“Excuse me? The guy you knocked out yesterday is back!” \n
“Come in, Child” \n
I walked inside to a surprisingly roomy home. There was a staircase that led underneath the ground that spread into a much larger area, full of old books and plants. She was sitting up top, cross-legged on the floor, in front of a fire. I walked in and sat down across from her. She reached her hand out and a pile of water appeared above me and came down and soaked my entire body.\n
“What are you doing sitting around doing nothing! We can’t even start defending our world because you are so weak! Get out of my home and go kill 20 creatures in the forest if you even can! Don’t come back until you are done!” \n
I stood up and shook myself off, while I was shaking myself off she pointed a finger and a small shock hit my body. I jumped. She kept at it, created larger streams of electricity. Soon I was sprinting in the direction of the exit. I reached the outside world and breathed a sigh of relief. Time to go to the forest. I had never killed anything before. I did not even know that I could. But I gathered my courage as I walked to town. \n


    </string>

    <string name="story8">
        "Finish your current quest"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_sign_up">SignUpActivity</string>
    <string name="emailHint">Email</string>

</resources>
